yadig.com 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy - YaDig.com

#### Collection and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

This privacy policy (Privacy Policy), together with the Terms of Use in relation to this website (Site) and any other documents referred to in it, sets out the basis on which any personal data YaDig (we, us, our) collects from customers, visitors and users of the Site (you, your), or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how it will be treated.

We value the relationship we have with you, and we are committed to responsible information handling practices. We take your privacy very seriously and want you to feel comfortable whenever you visit the Site or provide us with your personal information. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, then you must stop using or accessing the Site. 

#### Notice of Information Practices

We collect two types of information about our users and all visitors to the Site: (1) personally-identifiable information provided by you as well as information we learn about you from your use of our services and the Site; and (2) aggregate information that can’t be used to identify a particular visitor (see "Cookies" section below).

We collect personally-identifiable information about you only when you specifically give it to us (for example, when registering a YaDig.com account). YaDig does not store any credit card or related transactional information. We do not disclose this information to third parties except as required to provide services to you, to carry out the transactions you have requested, to operate the Site, or as required by law or any court of competent jurisdiction. 

We may collect additional information from you in relation to promotions that we run, and also any information you provide when corresponding with us.

We, or third parties specifically selected by us, may use your information for the following purposes:

  * Ensuring that the Content of the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * Providing you with information or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * Notifying you about changes to the Site or our services, where applicable.

Your information will be held at our internal servers or at the premises of another appointed third party. We may allow other third parties to have access to your information, but only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Protecting Your Personal Information

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site. Any transmission of data is at your risk.

We recognise industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorised access and misuse. All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Any payment transactions will be protected and safeguarded by encryption during data transit and storage. We will not disclose to third parties any personally identifiable information that you provide without your consent, except as necessary to provide services you have specifically requested. Once we have received your information, we will use industry standard procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access to that information.

#### Common Web Technologies

We employ common web technologies that help to manage the Site, among them:

  * Cookies – A "cookie" is a name for tokens of information that the Site may provide to your web browser, which is used only by the Site while you are at that website. The Site uses cookies for a variety of purposes. Cookies are used to help us better understand website usage in the aggregate to ascertain which areas of the Site users prefer. We also use cookies to simplify your data entry for certain online forms. If you simply want to browse, you do not have to accept cookies from the Site. If you decide, however, that you would like to register and log in to special areas of the Site, and you have modified your browser settings not to accept cookies, you will need to re-set your browser to accept the cookies that are sent to it. Otherwise, you may not be able to participate in certain areas of the Site. Most browsers are by default set to accept and maintain cookies.
  * Website Usage Data – With or without cookies, the Site keeps track of usage data, such as the source address that a page request is coming from (i.e., your IP address and domain name), date and time of the page request, the referring website (if any), and other parameters in the URL (e.g., search criteria). We may use this data to better understand website usage in the aggregate to determine which areas of the Site users prefer (e.g., based on the number of visits to those areas), and we may make this aggregated information available to third parties as part of our business. This information is stored in log files and used for aggregated and statistical reporting. It is not attributed to you as an individual. 
  * Links to External Sites – This Privacy Policy only applies to the Site. Although the Site may provide links to websites of third parties, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website that you connect to from the Site. You must read their privacy policies to understand how they manage personal information. Although we choose our partners and sponsors carefully, we are not responsible for the Content or practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to or from the Site. These links are provided as a service to users of the Site. Unless otherwise stated, they do not constitute any endorsement, sponsorship or approval of their Content, policies or practices. 

#### Disclosure Of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of the YaDig group of companies, which means our subsidiaries, our holding companies and their subsidiaries. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in the following circumstances: 

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  *   
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to:   
(a) comply with any legal obligation;   
(b) enforce or apply the Terms of Use and/or any other agreements; or   
(c) protect our rights, property or safety, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

#### Your Rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for marketing purposes or if we intend to disclose any of your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms used to collect your data. 

#### Your Consent

When you register to Yadig.com you will be providing a limited amount of information which we will store in a secure environment. The data that we hold for each customer is used in order to serve better content to each customer. Below is a list detailing what kind of information we store: 

Name and contact details   
Transaction history   
Communications record   
Profile: age, gender, profession, income, hobbies   
Spending habits 

We will not sell, store, share, rent or lease your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission, but we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the YADIG website.

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to this Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on the Site and, where appropriate, notified to you. Your continued use of the Site will be deemed to be your acceptance of any changes to this Privacy Policy.
